https://animaxdesigngroup.com/about/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Animax Design Group (ADG Creative Media Services) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.animaxdesigngroup.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by ADG Creative Media Services.
Personal identification information
We do collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
ADG Creative Media Services collects and uses User’s personal information for the following purposes:
– To improve our Site
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
– To send periodic emails
The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, they may do so by contacting us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, user-name, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
Changes to this privacy policy
ADG Creative Media Services has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage User’s to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site,
or your dealings with this Site, please contact us at:
Media
This document was last updated on November 06/2017
Privacy Policy was last modified:
November 24th, 2017 by Steven R. Noble
error: Content is protected !! ©1997-2020 - All Rights Reserved. ADG Creative Media Services
